[cheery music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[bell dinging]
- Okay, okay, order up.
[铃声]
=> - 好吧，好吧，订购。
[dinging continues]
[叮叮声继续]
[exhaust whooshes]
[排气管嘶嘶声]
[dinging]
- Uh, hello, Krusty Kitchen.
[叮叮]
- 呃，你好，库斯蒂厨房。
Hmm?
唔？
Hello?
你好？
It sounds like sleigh bells!
听起来像雪橇铃！
Is that you, Santa Claus?
是你吗，圣诞老人？
[grunts]
[咕哝]
I can still hear the ring... go.
我仍然能听到铃声……走吧。
Hm?
[strained grunt]
嗯？
[紧张的咕噜声]
[ringing continues]
[铃声继续]
Hmm.
No bells in here.
唔。
这里没有门铃。
Egh, this is serious.
呃，这件事很严重。
[whistling] And just where
do you think you're going
[口哨] 就在哪里
你觉得你要去吗
during business hours?
营业时间内？
Sorry, Mr. Krabs,
but I gotta see an ear doctor.
对不起，蟹老板，
但我得去看耳科医生。
I've been hearing
a ringing in my ears all week.
我一直听到
整个星期我的耳朵都嗡嗡作响。
Hold your sea horses, boy-o.
You don't have tinniterus.
抓住你的海马，小伙子。
你没有耳鸣。
- I don't?
- No.
- 我不知道？
- 不。
I've been ringing this bell
all week.
我已经敲响了这个钟
整个星期。
I'm doing it
to condition the customers.
我正在做
来调节顾客。
Whenever they hear the bell...
[bell rings]
每当他们听到铃声时...
[铃声响起]
They'll hunger
for a Krabby Patty
他们会挨饿
蟹肉饼
and come straight
to the Krusty Krab.
直来
到蟹堡王。
Oh!
哦！
I don't get it.
- Observe.
我不明白。
- 观察。
First, I condition them
while they're eating.
首先，我调节它们
当他们吃饭的时候。
[bell ringing]
[铃声响起]
Beat it, Quasimodo.
打败它，卡西莫多。
[chuckling]
Eh? Eh?
[轻笑]
呃？呃？
Eh? Eh, eh?
[giggling]
呃？呃，呃？
[咯咯笑]
I'm gonna go bop that guy!
我要去打败那个家伙！
Now, now, honey.
Think of the children.
现在，现在，亲爱的。
想想孩子们。
Oh, you're right, dear.
哦，你是对的，亲爱的。
What was I thinking?
我在想什么？
Kids, go bop that guy.
孩子们，去打败那个家伙吧。
- - Eh?
- Wha...
- - 呃？
- 世界卫生大会...
[yelps]
kids: [scream, grunt]
[尖叫声]
孩子们：[尖叫，咕噜声]
Mmm.
[burps]
嗯。
[打嗝]
[sighs]
[叹气]
Now this guy's
heard the bell before.
现在这个家伙的
之前听到铃声。
Watch him when I ring it.
[bell rings]
当我按铃时看着他。
[铃声响起]
Mmm-hmm-hmmm.
嗯嗯嗯。
[sinister music]
[险恶的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
I want another Krabby Patty.
我想要另一个蟹肉饼。
[gargles]
And a bucket for my saliva.
[漱口]
还有一个装我口水的桶。
Oh, can I ring the little bell?
哦，我可以按响小铃吗？
Can I, can I, can I?
我可以吗我可以吗我可以吗？
Ohh, you can do better
than that, boy-o.
哦，你可以做得更好
比那，男孩哦。
You can ring the big bell.
你可以按响大铃。
Ooh!
[strained grunting]
哦！
[紧张的咕哝声]
Eh...
呃……
Whoa! Huh?
[bell dinging]
哇！啊？
[铃声]
[clams chirping]
[蛤蜊鸣叫]
[foreboding music]
[不祥的音乐]
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
Krabby Patty...
克拉比帕蒂...
[all yelp]
[大家尖叫]
[bell dinging]
[铃声]
[all gargling]
[全部漱口]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[ringing continues]
[铃声继续]
[all gargling]
[全部漱口]
Huh?
啊？
[gargling]
Krabby Patties...
[漱口]
蟹黄饼...
all: Krabby Patties.
Krabby Patties.
全部：蟹肉饼。
蟹肉饼。
["What Shall We do with
a Drunken Sailor" plays]
[“我们该怎么办
喝醉的水手》播放]
[register dings]
[登记叮叮声]
[bell dings]
[铃声]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[whining]
[抱怨]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
不，不，不，不，不，不，不！
No!
不！
[screams]
[bell rattles]
[尖叫声]
[铃声响起]
[all clamoring]
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
[全都吵闹]
- 不，不，不，不，不，不，不！
What the halibut
is wrong with you, boy?
什么是大比目鱼
小伙子，你有什么问题吗？
[grunts]
[咕哝]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
不，不，不，不，不，不，不！
He's lost his mind.
他失去了理智。
He never had a mind.
他从来没有头脑。
Oh, I've seen this before.
哦，我以前见过这个。
I know what to do.
Yah!
我知道该怎么做。
啊！
No, no, no, no!
不，不，不，不！
No, no!
No, no, no...
不，不！
不，不，不……
[exhales]
[呼气]
When Patrick has
a tantrum like this,
当帕特里克有
像这样发脾气，
jellyfish jelly on the belly
肚子上的水母果冻
is the only thing
that calms him down.
是唯一的事情
这让他平静下来。
Then when he comes out of it,
he hardly remembers a thing.
然后当他从其中走出来的时候，
他几乎什么都不记得了。
Hey, buddy.
Feel better?
嘿，伙计。
感觉好些了吗？
What's the last thing
you remember?
最后一件事是什么
你还记得吗？
Uh, I remember
呃，我记得
hearing a bell ring.
听到铃声响起。
When I was a little sea star,
当我还是一只小海星时，
and... and it was time
for my bath,
而且...是时候了
为了我的洗澡，
My parents would always
ring a bell.
我的父母总是会
响铃。
It's bath time, son.
儿子，洗澡时间到了。
I... I didn't want a bath.
我...我不想洗澡。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
不，不，不，不，不，不，不！
No, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
不，不，不！
不，不，不，不，不！
After that, the only thing
I remember is nothin'.
之后，唯一的事情就是
我记得没什么。
Then it's time for me
to be proactive
那么我的时间到了
积极主动
and help my buddy here.
并在这里帮助我的朋友。
I am going to silence
我要沉默
every ding-dong bell in town,
starting with...
城里的每一声叮咚钟声，
开始于...
[grunts]
This one.
[咕哝]
这个。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
And this one!
还有这个！
Wait, how'd you get
so strong all of a sudden?
等等，你怎么得到的
突然这么强？
Through the power of friendship!
通过友谊的力量！
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
Look out,
bells of Bikini Bottom.
当心，
比基尼泳裤的铃铛。
SpongeBob is about to silence
every ring,
海绵宝宝即将沉默
每一个戒指，
chime, buzz, and jingle jangle.
钟声、嗡嗡声和叮当声。
Hyah-ha! [heroic music]
哈哈！ [英雄音乐]
There goes a dear darling dude.
一个亲爱的家伙走了。
There goes
my brilliant bell business.
那里去了
我辉煌的钟生意。
You know, Pat-O,
你知道，帕特奥，
I was studying
your impressive moves
我正在学习
你令人印象深刻的举动
during your little,
um, acrimony.
在你小的时候，
嗯，尖酸刻薄。
My little macaroni?
我的小通心粉？
Yeah, that's right,
and I believe that I have a way
是的，没错，
我相信我有办法
to make back all the money
I'm gonna lose.
赚回所有的钱
我会输的。
One million dollars
to the challenger
一百万美元
致挑战者
that can beat Harry the Health
Hazard in supreme fighting.
可以打败健康哈利
最高战斗中的危险。
[laughs]
[笑]
[radical rock music]
[激进摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Not the pretzel!
[whimpers]
不是椒盐卷饼！
[呜咽]
Hoo-yah!
呼呀！
[hums]
[哼哼]
[chomps]
[咀嚼]
- [squeals]
- [growls]
- [尖叫声]
- [咆哮]
That reminds me.
I'm still hungry.
这让我想起了。
我还饿着呢。
Got any more posters?
还有更多海报吗？
Knock yourself out.
把自己打垮。
We're gonna be
rolling in posters.
我们将会是
海报中滚动。
[chuckles]
[chomping]
[笑声]
[咀嚼]
[bell ringing]
[铃声响起]
Huh?
啊？
[heroic music]
[英雄音乐]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
For my buddy, Patrick!
为了我的朋友帕特里克！
[grunts, squeals]
[咕哝声、尖叫声]
[crowd screaming]
[人群尖叫]
[bike bell ringing]
[自行车铃声响起]
[panting]
- Hmm?
[气喘吁吁]
- 嗯？
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[monkey screeches]
[猴子尖叫声]
For my buddy, Patrick!
为了我的朋友帕特里克！
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
[cow moos]
For my buddy, Patrick!
[牛哞哞]
为了我的朋友帕特里克！
[worms barking]
[蠕虫吠叫]
[bell ringing]
[铃声响起]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[gurgling]
For Patrick!
[咕噜声]
为了帕特里克！
[boat horn honks]
[船喇叭鸣响]
- Okay, Patrick!
It's go time.
- 好吧，帕特里克！
出发时间到了。
- Are we changing our seats?
- Yeah.
- 我们要换座位吗？
- 是的。
I got you the best seat
in the house.
我给你安排了最好的座位
在房子里。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Ooh, this is the best seat
in the house.
哦，这是最好的座位
在房子里。
It's like 3D.
就像 3D 一样。
I can almost reach out
and touch the referee.
我几乎可以伸手
并触摸裁判。
- Hey!
- Duh-ow, ho, ho!
- 嘿！
- 嗬嗬，嗬，嗬！
Our next victim... er,
challenger, is...
我们的下一个受害者...呃，
挑战者，是……
Patrick Star!
帕特里克星！
[laughs]
[笑]
The next victim
has the same name as me.
下一个受害者
和我同名。
Yeah, crazy right?
是啊，疯狂吧？
[bell dings]
[铃声]
Oh...
哦...
[screams] No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no!
[尖叫]不，不，
不，不，不，不，不，不！
Well, it looks like
the challenger
嗯，看起来像
挑战者
is doing a good job
of fighting with himself.
做得很好
与自己战斗。
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- Hm?
- 不，不，不，不，不，不，不！
- 嗯？
Huh?
啊？
[screams]
[grunts]
[尖叫声]
[咕哝]
Patricks:
Tweet, tweet, tweet, tweet.
帕特里克斯：
推文，推文，推文，推文。
[cackles]
[咯咯笑]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不！
[mumbling]
[咕哝]
[growls]
Yah!
[咆哮]
啊！
[screaming]
[尖叫]
[shouts]
No, no, no, no, no!
[喊叫]
不，不，不，不，不！
[both babbling]
[两人都胡言乱语]
No, no, no!
- [shrieks]
不，不，不！
- [尖叫]
No, no, no, no!
不，不，不，不！
[chomps]
[咀嚼]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- [grunts]
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不！
- [咕哝]
- No, no, no...
- Whew, there we are.
- 不，不，不……
- 哇，我们到了。
Whew.
呼。
Well, folks, I think
it looks like the fight's over.
好吧，伙计们，我想
看来战斗已经结束了。
- What happened?
- I just became rich.
- 发生了什么？
- 我刚刚变得富有。
[bell dings]
- Ooh...
[铃声]
- 哦...
Uh-oh. - No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
呃哦。 - 不，不，不，不，不，不，不！
Whoa!
[grunts]
哇！
[咕哝]
[wheezing]
For my buddy, Patrick.
[喘息]
为了我的朋友帕特里克。
[groans]
I did it, pal.
[呻吟]
我做到了，朋友。
I silenced every bell in town
我让镇上的每一个钟声都安静了
so that you will no longer
have a tantrum,
让你不再
发脾气，
buddy.
伙伴。
Aw, thank you, best friend.
噢，谢谢你，最好的朋友。
Aww.
哇。
I don't care about bells ringing
我不在乎铃声的响起
or conditioning
customers anymore...
或调理
顾客不再...
♪ 'Cause I got
a million dollars ♪
♪ 因为我得到了
一百万美元♪
[chuckles]
[笑声]
[slow-motion cash register ding]
【慢动作收银叮】
[slow-motion] Uh-oh!
[慢动作] 呃哦！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Oh, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no!
哦，不，不，不，
不，不，不，不，不！
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不！
No!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
不！
不，不，不，不，不，不，不！
[both grunt]
[两人咕哝]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不！
No, no, no, no!
不，不，不，不！
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no! [whimpers]
不，不，不，不，
不，不，不！ [呜咽]
Hello, son.
We saw you fighting today...
你好，儿子。
今天我们看到你们打架了...
On the TV.
We're so proud.
在电视上。
我们非常自豪。
Oh, hi, Mr. and Mrs. Star.
噢，嗨，斯塔先生和斯塔太太。
I know you were loving parents,
我知道你们是慈爱的父母，
but you really messed up
your kid by ringing a bell
但你真的搞砸了
你的孩子按响铃
whenever it was time
for his bath.
每当时间到的时候
为他洗澡。
Bell?
We never rang a bell.
钟？
我们从来没有按过门铃。
Yeah.
Never.
是的。
绝不。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
You never rang a bell?
你从来没有按过门铃吗？
[laughing] No.
Don't you remember?
[笑]不。
你不记得了吗？
We would squeeze
your rubber duck.
我们会挤
你的橡皮鸭。
[gasps]
My rubber duck?
[喘气]
我的橡皮鸭？
- Yes, this one.
- [cooing]
- 是的，就是这个。
- [咕咕声]
Aw, kind of gets you
right in your heart's kitchen,
噢，有点明白你的意思
就在你心中的厨房，
doesn't it, Mr. Krabs?
不是吗，蟹老板？
Well, I think I can tape it
all back together.
嗯，我想我可以把它录下来
全部回到一起。
Ducky.
I wonder if it still quacks.
鸭子。
我想知道它是否还在嘎嘎叫。
[quacks]
[庸医]
Whoa, whib, whib, whib, whib!
哇，呜呜，呜呜，呜呜，呜呜！
Whib, whib, whib, whib, whib!
- Oh, here we go again!
呜呜，呜呜，呜呜，呜呜，呜呜！
- 哦，我们又来了！
[laughs]
[笑]
[monkey screeching]
[猴子尖叫]